Finding Aid for Dave Siglin papers, 1968-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Dave Siglin papers 1968-2008
Siglin, Dave.
2 oversized volumes
3 linear feet (in 5 boxes)
2009115 Aa 2
Program Director at the Ark, Ann Arbor, Michigan music club; administrative records relating to the management of the Ark, including artists’ contracts and financial records, printed materials such as concert calendars, flyers, and posters, and photographs of Ark performances, informal snapshots and publicity photos of performers.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The papers were donated by Dave Siglin (donor no. 10045 ) in 2008.
Periodic additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Dave Siglin served as Program Director for the Ark, an Ann Arbor music venue from 1968 until his retirement in March of 2008.
The Ark was established in 1965 as an outreach ministry--a coffeehouse--by five local churches: Northside Presbyterian Church, First Presbyterian Church, Calvary Presbyterian Church, Campus Chapel, and Presbyterian Campus Center. Though the Ark began as a partnership between religious organizations, the purpose of the Ark was not evangelism. Rather, the Ark founders wanted to provide university students with a safe, substance-free space where music, discussion, and artistic expression could thrive, and a respite from the turbulent campus climate of the mid 1960s. The Ark's mission statement is as follows: "The Ark is a non-profit organization dedicated to the enrichment of the human spirit through the presentation, preservation and encouragement of folk, roots and ethnic music and related arts. The Ark provides a safe and welcoming atmosphere for all people to listen to, learn about, perform and share music."
Under Siglin's management, the Ark became a folk music institution, with many of the major folk artists of the 1960s-2000s performing at the Ark. Folk music continues to be one of the many musical styles presented at the Ark. Since its inception in 1965, the Ark has had three different homes: the first at the former Adams House at 1421 Hill Street. During the late 1970s, funding from the Ark's founding churches was discontinued and the Ark was reorganized as 501(3) non-profit organization; shortly after the reorganization, the Ark moved to its second site at 637 1/2 S. Main Street. The Ark opened at its the current location at 316 S. Main Street in 1996.
The Ark continues to provide public music events as a non-profit organization. Anya Siglin, Dave and Linda Siglin's daughter is currently the Ark's Program Director.
The Dave Siglin papers date from 1968-2008 and primarily document Siglin's management role at the Ark, an Ann Arbor music club. The papers have been arranged into three series: Administrative Records; Printed Materials; and Photographs.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Social life and customs.; Ark (Nightclub); Folk music--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Siglin, Dave.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Ark (Nightclub); Folk music--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Music concerts--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Siglin, Dave.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Posters.
- Administrative Records
  Administrative Records contain artists' contracts for musicians who performed at the Ark, financial records, and a 1976 contract between the City of Ann Arbor and Dave Siglin that addresses the Ark's newly acquired non-profit status. The series also includes correspondence addressed to Dave and Linda Siglin. Financial records are part of this series and are most comprehensive for 1969 until the early 1970s, though scattered dates are represented in the collection. An oversized financial ledger also comprises part of this series.
  - Ann Arbor Comprehensive Employment Program, Ark Coffeehouse and City of Ann Arbor 1976 (Box 1)
  - Ark Financial Records 1972-1986 (Box 1)
    (scattered dates)
  - Ark Financial Ledger January 1969-August 1972 (Volume 1)
  - Artists' Contracts, A-Z, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
    (Incoming correspondence to Dave and Linda Siglin)
- Printed Materials
  Printed Materials contain monthly concert calendars from 1969-1982, bi-monthly event calendars from 1984-2008, concert flyers from 1969, 1972-1976, a news clipping file with various articles about the Ark, and miscellaneous printed matter. An outsized volume contains concert posters and flyers from 1978-1986.
  - Ark Concert Flyers
    - 1969, 1972-1976 (Box 1)
  - Ark Concert Posters and Flyers, 1978-1986 (Volume 2)
  - Ark Monthly Concert Calendars (Box 1)
    - 1969-1982 (Box 1)
  - Ark Bimonthly Calendar of Events October 1984-December 2004 (Box 1)
  - Ark Bimonthly Calendar of Events 2005-2008 (scattered dates) (Box 1)
  - Patrons of the Ark and list of benefit performers
    - July 1977-April 1981 (Box 1)
  - News clipping file (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Photographs
  Photographs contain images of performers and audiences during Ark concerts. Candid shots are included as well. There are two folders of photographs depicting Dave and Linda Siglin. Separate from photographs taken at the Ark are the publicity photos produced by performers’ publicists and distributed for use in press and publicity materials. Photographs are arranged alphabetically. When the item contains the note "see also" this means that another image of that performer is contained among the images of another performer. The bulk of the photographs date from the early 1970s until the late 1980s.
  - Dave and Linda Siglin, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Ark Performers and Audiences (arranged alphabetically), 35 folders
    - A
      - The Aging Children (with Rich Del Grosso and Leo Kretzner) (Box 2)
      - Amram, David (with David Bernstein) (Box 4)
      - Anderson, O.J. (Box 2)
      - Appleton, Vikki (with Dick Kiesling) (Box 2)
    - B, 2 folders
      - Badieux, Edmund (Box 2)
      - Badieux, Quentin (Box 2)
        (see also Badieux, Edmund)
      - Bailey, Amanda (with Nora Goddeyne and Dick Siegel) (Box 2)
      - Bain, Aly (Box 2)
        (also in oversize box 4)
        (see also Boys of the Lough)
      - Baldwin, Luke (Box 2)
      - Balfa Brothers (Box 2)
      - Baran, Roma (with Anna McGarrigle) (Box 2)
      - Barker, Linda (with Dale Bellaire, Shelly Bellaire and Don Jones in Edward Albee's "A Delicate Balance") (Box 2)
      - Bashour, Jeanie Dovell (with Carmen Caballaro, David Douglass, Beth Gilgrod, Patrick Hill and Michael Lynn) (Box 2)
      - Bellamy, Peter (Box 2)
      - Bensusan, Pierre (Box 2)
      - Betty (with Alyson Palmer, Amy Ziff and Bitsy Ziff) (Box 2)
      - Bia Bichinis Dance Company (Box 2)
      - Bierl, Ray (Box 2)
      - Bigford, Bill (Box 2)
      - Binder, Roy Book (Box 2)
      - Blake, Norman (with Nancy Blake) (Box 2)
      - Blind Jim Brewer (Box 2)
      - Bloom, Ken (Box 2)
      - Bloom, Jan (Box 2)
      - Bok, Gordon (Box 2)
        (see also Dodge, Marshall; Zentz, Bob)
      - Bookeloo, Jason (Box 3)
      - Bosom Buddies (with Marcy Marxer and Karrie Potter) (Box 2)
      - Bothy Band (with Kevin Burke, Paddy Keenan, Donal Lunny, Matt Malloy, Triona Ni O'Domhnaill and Micheál O'Domhnaill) (Box 2)
      - Bowen, Peter (Box 2)
      - Bowers, Bryan (Box 2)
        (see also Blake, Norman)
      - Boys of the Lough (with Aly Bain, Jean Carignon, Cathal McConnell, Robin Morton and Dave Richardson) (Box 2)
      - Bradley, Hank (with Jody Stecher), 2 images (Box 2)
      - Brand, Oscar (Box 3)
      - Breckman, Andy (Box 2)
      - Broad, Julian (with Judy Dyki) (Box 2)
      - Brody, Saul (Box 2)
      - Bryant, "Uncle" Ed (Box 2)
      - Burgh, Steve (Box 2)
        (see also Bromberg, David)
      - Burns, Martha (with Julia Mainer, Ruth Menlebaum) (Box 2)
        (see also Sinclair Brothers)
    - Barrand, Tony (with John Roberts) (Box 2)
      (see also Grossman, Stephan)
    - Bromberg, David (with Norman Blake, Nancy Bromberg, Debbie Dodd, Jonathan Dorn, Peter Ecklund, Dick Fegy, Jack Herrick, Norman Kennedy, Dough Kershaw, Larry Packer, Neill Rossi, Jay Ungar) (Box 2)
    - C
      - Cahn, David (Box 2)
        (see also Bailey, Amanda; Burns, Martha)
      - Calhoun, Judy (with Marla Camp, Kathy O'Neill, Dick Reuss, Jo Reuss, Anya Siglin) (Box 2)
      - Cameron, John Alan (Box 2)
      - Carawan, Guy (Box 4)
      - Carignan, Jean (with Giles Losier) (Box 2)
        (also in oversize box 3)
      - Carthy, Martin (with John Kirkpatrick) (Box 2)
      - Chapman, Sam (Box 2)
      - Chenille Sisters (with Connie Huber, Grace Morand and Cheryl Dawdy) (Box 3)
      - Cherish the Ladies (Box 2)
      - Chin, Charlie (Box 2)
      - Christl, Margaret (with Grit Laskin and Ian Robb) (Box 2)
      - Clairseach (with Ann and Carlie Heymann) (Box 2)
      - Clark, Nora (with Keith Clark) (Box 2)
      - Cohen, John (Box 2)
        (see also New Lost City Ramblers)
      - Cotton, Elizabeth (Box 3)
    - Clark, Pam (with Ann Feiker, Jim Feiker, Marge Himel, Larry Klein, and Bill Mullin) (Box 2)
      (see also Edmunds, Steve)
    - Cohen, Andy (Box 2)
    - Cooney, Michael (with Tony Barrand, John Eberhardt, Joe Hickerson, Kate Nixon, and Andy Wallace) (Box 2)
    - D
      - Danforth, Percy "Mr. Bones" (with Gemini) (Box 4)
      - Davis, (Rev.) Gary (Box 2)
      - Dawson, Smoke (Box 2)
        (see also McGarrigle, Kate)
      - DeDannan (with Jackie Daly, Alee Finn, Frankie Gavin, Maura O'Connell and Charlie Piggot) (Box 2)
      - DeLoach, Chris (with Martha Rupaw) (Box 2)
      - Dodge, Marshall (with Tony Saletan) (Box 2)
      - Dodge, Marshall (with Linda Siglin) (Box 2)
      - Double Decker Stringband (Box 2)
    - E
      - Elliott, Jack (Box 2)
        (see also Baldwin, Luke)
      - Edmondson, Suzanne (Box 2)
      - Edmunds, Steve (with David Jans) (Box 2)
        (see also Clark, Pam)
    - F
      - Fahey, John (Box 2)
      - Farina, Mimi (Box 2)
      - Fiddlepuppets (Box 2)
      - Fisher, Archie (Box 2)
      - Fleck, Bela (with New Grass Revival) (Box 2)
      - Franke, Bob (Box 2)
      - Freiheit, Karla (Box 2)
      - Friends of Fiddler's Green (with Alistair Brown, Tam Kearney, Grit Laskin, David Parry, Ian Robb and Lawrence Stevenson) (Box 2)
    - G
      - Gallagher, Mickey (Box 2)
      - Garvey, Victoria (with Pat Garvey) (Box 2)
      - Geer, Will (with Dick Wingfield) (Box 2)
      - Gensemer, Bob (with Matt Watroba) (Box 2)
      - Gerard, Alice (Box 2)
      - Geremia, Paul (Box 2)
      - Gibson, Bob (Box 2)
      - Gifford, Paul (with Helen Gross and Bob Spinner) (Box 2)
      - Gilfellon, Tom (with Alistair Anderson and Colin Ross) (Box 2)
      - Goddeyne, Nora (Box 2)
      - The Golden Ring (with George Armstrong, Harry Guffey and Harry Tuft) (Box 2)
      - Goodman, Steve (with Henry the Fiddlers and Kris Kristofferson, and with Michael Cooney) (Box 2)
        (see also The Golden Ring)
      - Gorka, John (Box 2)
      - Green Grass Cloggers (Box 2)
      - Grey, Sara (with Roger Renwick and Andy Wallace) (Box 2)
      - Grisso, Kasia (with Guerin Wilkinson) (Box 2)
      - Grossman, Stephan (with Herb David and John Roberts) (Box 2)
      - Gurdy, Hurdy (Box 2)
      - Guruitz, Paul (Box 2)
      - Guthrie, Arlo (Box 2)
      - Guthrie, Jeff (Box 2)
    - H
      - Hammond, John (Box 2)
      - Handle, Johnny (with Colin Ross) (Box 2)
        (see also Gilfellon, Tom)
      - Hanks, Larry (with Roger Renwick) (Box 2)
        (see also Cooney, Michael; Grey, Sara; Hickerson, Joe; Hinton, Sam)
      - Hardy, Lyndon (with Jay Ungar) (Box 2)
      - Harmony Grits (with Gary Hussar, Ed Maggio, Mike O'Laughlin and Charlie Roehrig) (Box 2)
      - Heaney, Joe (Box 2)
      - Heaton, Lynn (Box 2)
      - Hedges, Michael (Box 2)
      - Herdman, Priscilla (Box 2)
      - Hickerson, Joe (with Genny Haley and Roger Renwick) (Box 2)
        (see also Cooney, Michael; Grey, Sara)
      - Hicks, Noel (Box 2)
      - High Level Ranters (Box 2)
      - Himel, Marjorie (with Larry Klein) (Box 2)
      - Hinkley, Bill (with Andy Stein) (Box 2)
      - Hinton, Sam (Box 2)
        (see also Cooney, Michael; Dodge, Marshall)
      - Honolulu Heartbreaker (with Dyan Firth, Eileen Tobin and Marion Tobin) (Box 2)
      - Hooter (Box 2)
      - Hot Mud Family (Box 4)
      - House Band (with Ged Foley and John Skelton) (Box 2)
      - Huxtable, Christensen and Hood (Box 2)
    - I
      - Interlochen group with Dave Siglin and others (Box 2)
      - Irvine, Andy (Box 2)
        (see also Patrick Street)
      - Ives, Sandy (Box 2)
    - J
      - Jabbour, Alan (Box 2)
        (see also Hickerson, Joe)
      - Jackson, Buster (Box 2)
        (see also Guthrie, Jeff)
      - Jackson, John (Box 2)
        (see also McBride, Owen)
      - Janes, Loning (Box 2)
      - UM-Japanese Music Study Group (Box 2)
      - Johns, David (with Larry Klein) (Box 2)
        (see also Clark, Pam; DeLoach, Chris)
      - Johnson, Craig (with Bill Schmitt, Dick Terrier and Vinnie Tufo) (Box 2)
        (see also Cahn, David)
      - Jones, Bessie Sea Island Singers) (Box 2)
      - Jessie Jones (with Georgette Jones and cousin) (Box 2)
    - K
      - Kahoots (with Julie Austin, Bill Barton and Gary Reynolds) (Box 2)
      - Kamalay, Ray (Box 2)
      - Karmazin, Anne Marie (with Anne Jackson) (Box 2)
        (see also Appleton, Vikki; Freiheit, Karla)
      - Katz, Nancy (Box 2)
        (see also Killen, Louis; New Lost City Ramblers)
      - Keelaghan, James (with Cathy Cook) (Box 2)
      - Keith, Bill (Box 2)
      - Keller, Sarah Melton (includes negatives) (Box 2)
        (see also DeLoach, Chris)
      - Kellie, Mike (of Parrish and Gurvitz) (Box 2)
      - Kendall, Gail (with Larry Unger) (Box 2)
        (see also Calhoun, Judy; Clark, Pam; Himel, Marjorie)
      - Kennedy, Norman (Box 2)
      - Killen, Louis (Box 2)
        (see also Cooney, Michael; Heaney, Joe)
      - Klezmorim (Box 2)
      - Koerner, Spider John (with daughter) (Box 2)
      - Koppel, George (Box 2)
      - Kossoy, Irene (Box 2)
      - Kretzner, Leo (Box 2)
        (see also The Aging Children)
      - Kweskin, Jim (Box 2)
    - L
      - Lamontagne, Alain (Box 2)
      - Lavin, Christine (Box 2)
      - Ledbetter, Huddie "Leadbelly" (Box 2)
      - Losier, Giles (Box 4)
      - Luksch, Paul (Box 2)
        (see also Cohen, Andy)
    - M, 2 folders
      - Madison, Bill (Box 2)
      - Mainer, Wade (with Julia Mainer and Bill Meyer), 3 items (Box 2)
        (see also Burns, Martha)
      - Mandel, Rob't (Box 2)
      - Markellis, Tony (Box 2)
        (see also Amram, David; Bromberg, David)
      - Mathews, Wall (Box 2)
      - McBride, Owen (with Jim Strickland) (Box 2)
        (also in oversize box 5)
        (see also Dodge, Marshall; Heaney, Joe)
      - McCutcheon, John (Box 2)
      - McConnell, Cathal (Box 2)
      - McGlynn, Arty (Box 2)
        (See also Patrick Street)
      - McGarrigle, Kate (Box 2)
        (see also Baran, Roma; Dawson, Smoke)
      - McGraw, Hugh (Box 2)
      - McGuinn, Pat (Box 2)
      - McKenna, Antoinette (Box 2)
      - McKenna, Joe (Box 2)
      - Menard, D. L. (Box 2)
      - Meyer, Bill (with Joan Hellman) (Box 2)
        (see also Burns, Martha; Cahn, David; Johnson, Craig; Sinclair Brothers)
      - Meyer, Ruth (Box 2)
      - Mohr, Carol (Box 2)
      - Morse, Kendall (Box 2)
      - Morton, Robin (Box 2)
      - Muldaur, Maria (Box 2)
    - Marcovitz, Diana (Box 2)
    - N
      - Near, Holly (Box 2)
      - Neustadt, Lisa (Box 2)
      - New Lost City Ramblers (with Abby Miller, Anya Siglin and Jack Werner) (Box 2)
      - Newcomer, Carrie (Box 3)
      - Null, Lisa (Box 2)
    - O
      - O'Driscoll, Trasa (Box 2)
      - O'Neill, Barry (with Anya Siglin; Margaret Christl; and w/ Frankie Armstrong), 4 items (Box 2)
        (see also Calhoun, Judy; Clark, Pam; Cooney, Michael; Grey, Sara; Hanks, Larry; Hickerson, Joe; Killen, Louis)
      - Ohrlin, Glen (Box 2)
        (see also Kennedy, Norman)
      - Ostergren, Pam (Box 2)
        (see also Grey, Sara; Hickerson, Joe; New Lost City Ramblers)
    - P
      - Palazzola, Deedee (Box 2)
      - Parker, Chet (Box 2)
      - Parrish, Brian (of Parrish and Gurvitz with Mike Kelly and Rick Wills) (Box 2)
      - Patrick Street (with Kevin Burke, Jackie Daly, Arty McGlynn) (Box 2)
        (see also Irvine, Andy, Arty McGlynn
      - Paxton, Tom (Box 2)
      - Peirce, Maggie (Box 2)
      - Perlman, David (with Sivi Rae Shein and Linda Siglin) (Box 2)
        (see also Calhoun, Judy)
      - Phillips, Cyril (see also Barrand, Tony) (Box 2)
      - Phillips, Utah (with Steve Newhouse) (Box 2)
        (see also Baldwin, Luke; Brody, Saul; Dodge, Marshall; The Golden Ring, McBride, Owen)
      - Pierce, Otis (Box 2)
      - Posen, Shelley (with Jack Sheckman) (Box 2)
      - Possum Trot String Band (with Allen Barnes, Heath Curdts, Don Minnerly) (Box 2)
      - Post, Jim (Box 5)
      - Prine, Dave (of the National Recovery Act with Tyler Wilson) (Box 2)
      - Prine, John, 3 items (Box 2)
    - Q
      - Queen Ida (with the Bon Temps Zydeco Band) (Box 2)
      - Quine, Jack (Box 2)
        (see also Clark, Pam; Himel, Marjorie; Johns, David)
    - R
      - Redbone, Leon (Box 2)
      - Redpath, Jean (Box 2)
      - Reed, Ola Belle (Box 2)
      - Reich, Rowena (Box 2)
      - Reynolds, Malvina (with Jack Elliott) (Box 2)
      - Reynolds, Pat (Box 2)
      - RFD Boys (with Steve Whelan, Willard Spencer and Charlie Roehrig) (Box 5)
      - Rice, Toney (Box 3)
      - Richardson, Dave (Box 5)
      - Ritchie, Jean (with Mary and Steve Addiss) (Box 3)
      - Ringer, Jim (with Mary McCaslin; and with Glenn Ohrlin) (Box 2)
      - Robb, Ian (Box 2)
      - Rogers, Andy (Box 2)
        (see also Bromberg, David; Cohen, Andy; McGuinn, Pat)
      - Rogers, Gamble (Box 2)
      - Rose, Biff (Box 2)
        (also in oversize box 3 and oversize box 5)
      - Rosenbaum, Art (Box 2)
      - Rusconi, Pat (Box 2)
      - Rush, Tom (Box 2)
      - Ruth, Peter "Madcat" (Box 2)
        (see also Bookeloo, Jason; Bromberg, David; Johnson, Craig)
      - Ryan, Des (Box 2)
    - S, 2 folders
      - Saletan, Irene (Box 2)
        (see also Dodge, Marshall)
      - Sanders, Ron (Box 2)
      - Sands, Tommy (Box 2)
      - Savoy, Mark (Box 2)
      - Schilling, Jean (with Lee Schilling) (Box 2)
      - Schneter, Helen (Box 2)
      - Schwarz, Tracey (with Eloise Schwarz) (Box 2)
      - Schwartz, Willie (with Miriam Strum) (Box 2)
      - Sciaky, Carla (Box 2)
      - Seeger, Alice (Box 2)
      - Seeger, Mike (Box 2)
        (see also Kennedy, Norman; New Lost City Ramblers; Seeger, Alice)
      - Seeger, Pete (Box 2)
      - Shute, Bill (Box 2)
        (see also Null, Lisa)
      - Siebel, Paul (Box 2)
        (see also Bailey, Amanda)
      - Siglin, Dave (Box 2)
        (see also Bromberg, David; Calhoun, Judy; Clark, Pam; Cooney, Michael; Killen, Louis; New Lost City Ramblers; Reynolds, Pat; White, Bob)
      - Siglin, Linda (Box 2)
        (see also Baran, Roma; Bloom, Jan; Calhoun, Judy; Clark, Pam; Dodge Marshal, Garvey, Victoria; The Golden Ring; Grossman, Stephan; Guthrie, Jeff; Handle, Johnny; Hickerson, Joe; Honolulu Heartbreaker; Killen, Louis; New Lost City Ramblers; Parrish, Brian; Perlman, David; Rogers, Andy; Travis, Merle; Whiteley, Ken)
      - Sinclair Brothers (Box 2)
      - Skunk's Misery Stringband (Box 2)
      - Sky, Patrick (Box 2)
      - Smith, Bev (Box 2)
      - Smith, Michael (with Barbara Barrow) (Box 5)
      - Smith, Mike (Box 2)
        (see also Quine, Jack)
      - Sorrels, Rosalie (Box 2)
      - Spaelimenninir (Box 2)
      - Staines, Bill (Box 2)
      - Statman, Andy (Box 2)
      - Stecher, Jody (Box 2)
      - Jay Steilstra (Box 2)
      - Stein, Andy (Box 2)
        (see also Hinkley, Bill)
      - Stoll, Alan (Box 2)
      - Sundell, Jon (Box 2)
      - Sykes, Roosevelt (Box 2)
    - Sinclair Brothers (Box 2)
    - Sorrels, Rosalie (with Harry Tuft) (Box 2)
      (see also Bloom, Jan; Bromberg, David; DeLoach, Chris)
    - T
      - Taj Mahal (Box 2)
      - Thomas, Bobi (Box 2)
        (see also Bloom, Jan; New Lost City Ramblers; Ostergren, Pam)
      - Travis, Merle (Box 2)
      - Trickett, Ed (with Harry Tuft) (Box 2)
    - U
      - Ungar, Jay (Box 2)
      - Unidentified female singer (Box 2)
    - V
      - Van Ronk, Dave (Box 5)
      - Vanaver, Bill (with Lyvia Drapkin) (Box 2)
      - Voss, Jane (Box 2)
    - W
      - Wainwright, Loudon (Box 2)
      - The Watersons (Box 2)
      - Watson, Doc (with T. Michael Coleman and Jack Lawrence) (Box 2)
      - Watson, Jim (with Jack Herrick) (Box 5)
      - Werbin, Stan (Box 2)
      - West, Hedy (Box 2)
      - Wheeler, Cheryl (Box 2)
      - White, Bob (Box 2)
      - White, Bukka (Box 2)
      - Whiteley, Ken (Box 2)
        (see also Honolulu Heartbreaker)
      - Wilcox, John (Box 5)
      - Williams, LaRon (Box 2)
      - Wilson, George (Box 2)
    - X, Y, Z
      - Yacoub, Gabriel (Box 2)
      - Zentz, Bob (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
    (includes photographs of Ark Audiences)
  - Publicity photos (arranged alphabetically), 6 folders (Box 2)